(Howard:)You know, Amy took
some time off from him.
(Howard:)Really improved
their relationship.
(Raj:)Huh. Okay.
(Raj:)As long as it doesn't end
with us having coitus with him,
(Raj:)I'm in.
(Howard:)We should all take
a trip or something.
(Leonard:)You know, Penny and
I have been talking
(Leonard:)about taking a
weekend in Vegas.
(Leonard:)Maybe we should all go.
(Howard:)Bernie would love that.
Oh! Ooh! Maybe we could get
(Raj:)one of those party buses
to take us there.
(Leonard:)That sounds really fun.
(Raj:)Yeah, that sounds fun.
(Raj:)A party-bus party don't stop.
Ooh! When I say “party,”
you say “bus.”
(Penny:)No. No.
(in rhythm): No. No!
(Leonard:)So, the guys and I
were talking about
(Leonard:)renting a party bus and
everyone going to Vegas.
(Penny:)Oh, that could be fun.
(Penny:)But just to be clear,
you mean a party bus
(Penny:)with booze and music, right,
(Penny:)not, like, juice boxes
and video games?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Leonard:)And Howard's birthday
was a drop-off party.
(Leonard:)You didn't have to stay.
(Penny:)Well, I'm in.
(Penny:)When are we going?
This weekend.
(Sheldon:)Oh, where are we going?